Guide to Columbia University Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00166
Cubberley Education Library
- Columbia University, 1891-1979; 1809 item(s) Bound with catalogs under Columbia College: Catalog for 1896/97. Bound together with label of "Columbia College Registers": Catalogs for 1897/98-1899/1900 Bound together: Catalogs for 1900/01 & 1901/02 Catalog for 1902/03 Bound together: Catalogs for 19
  - Teachers College, 1891-1972; 175 item(s) Circular of information for 1893/94-1895/96, 1897/98-1901 Annual reports, extracts for 1894/95 Handbook for 1898/99 Announcements for 1901/02-1919/20, 1921/22-1936/37, 1939/40-1960/61, 1962/63-1971/72 Preliminary Announcement School of Practical Arts for 
    - Teaching internships in secondary schools in Metropolitan New York, 1966; 1 item(s)
    - International Studies at Teachers College, 1966-1967; 1 item(s)
    - Annual report of the Center for Education in Africa, 1967-1968; 1 item(s)
    - A new program for educational leadership, 1 item(s)
  - Watson Scientific Computing Laboratory, 1946-1962; 14 item(s) Announcements for 1946/47-1957/58, 1959/60, 1961/62